A Guide to the Ford Foundation records, Grants Them-Tw FA732H FA732H
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Ford Foundation Grants - Them to Tw, 1937-2006
  - Tibetan Poverty Alleviation Fund, Inc. (09950109), 1998 November 01-2001 November 15 (Reel R8642)
    China; Women--Health and hygiene--China--Tibet Autonomous Region (China) Autonomous Region (China)
  - Tides Center (09600800), 1996 June 01-1999 January 31 (Reel R7903)
    SUPPORT FOR THE MEDIA VOTING PROJECT
  - Tides Center (09601336), 1996 July 01-1997 June 30 (Reel R7348)
    SUPPORT FOR THE GENDER VIOLENCE AND HEALTH INITIATIVE OF THE HEALTH AND DEVELOPMENT POLICY PROJECT
    Hempel, Margaret L.;Neuborne, Helen
  - Tides Center (09601377), 1996 July 01-1998 June 30 (Reel R7679)
    PARTIAL OPERATIONAL SUPPORT FOR AMERICANS FOR A SUSTAINABLE ECONOMY
    Governance And Public Policy Program [GPP];Rural Poverty & Resources Program [RPR]
    Lindblom, Lance E.;Olson, Jeffrey T.
  - Tides Center (09650711), 1996 May 01-1997 April 30 (Reel R8001)
    SUPPORT FOR STUDENTS FOR RESPONSIBLE BUSINESS' MBA INTERNSHIP PROGRAM WITH SEVEN MATURE CDC'S
  - Tides Center (09651265), 1996 August 01-1996 December 31 (Reel R7329)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT OF THE 1996 ANNUAL CONFERENCE OF GRANTMAKERS FOR CHILDREN, YOUTH AND FAMILIES
  - Tides Center (09700555), 1997 March 01-1999 August 31 (Reel R8419)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A PROJECT TO PROMOTE NUCLEAR SAFETY
    Russia; United States; Global
  - Tides Center (09700765), 1997 April 01-1999 March 31 (Reel R8067)
    SUPPORT FOR THE FOREST TRUST'S COORDINATION OF THE NATIONAL NETWORK OF FOREST PRACTITIONERS
  - Tides Center (09701242), 1997 June 01-1999 May 31 (Reel R8080)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE TIDES CENTER'S NATIVE LANDS PROJECT TO HELP STRENGTHEN INDIGENOUS PEOPLES' ORGANIZATIONS IN CENTRAL AMERICA (965-0203)
    Mexico and Central America (Mexico City);Human Rights
    $200,000.00;$142,706.46
    Barry, Deborah;Brown, Kimberli R.;Cox, Larry
  - Tides Center (09701257), 1997 May 01-1998 February 28 (Reel R8895)
    STUDENTS FOR RESPONSIBLE BUSINESS TO DEVELOP STRATEGIES FOR EXPOSING BUSINESS SCHOOL STUDENTS TO COMMUNITY AND ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT
  - Tides Center (09701374), 1997 September 01-1999 February 28 (Reel R7561)
    FOR ASSOCIATION FOR PROGRESSIVE COMMUNICATIONS FOR IMPLEMENTATION OF STRATEGIC PLAN TO CONSOLIDATE ITS WORLDWIDE NETWORKING ACTIVITY
    Brazil (Rio de Janeiro);Mexico and Central America (Mexico City);Andean Region and Southern Cone (Santiago);Southern Africa (Johannesburg);Russia (Moscow);PSJ - Office of the Vice President;Governance and Civil Society;India, Nepal and Sri Lanka (New Delh
    $300,000.00;$208,500.00
    Batliwala, Srilatha;Brooke, Nigel P.;Capistrano, Ana Doris;Collins, Norman R.;Gerhart, John D.;Kedzie, Christopher R.
  - Tides Center (09701664), 1997 August 01-2001 July 31 (Reel R8693)
    CONTINUED SUPPORT FOR THE COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE OF STUDENTS FOR RESPONSIBLE BUSINESS (950-0946)
  - Tides Center (09750327), 1996 March 28-1997 March 27 (Reel R7912)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE PRECOLLEGIATE EDUCATION PROGRAM
  - Tides Center (09851768), 1998 June 01-1998 November 30 (Reel R8072)
    CAPACITY BUILDING, RES, INFO DISSEMINATION & NETWORKING ON ISSUES RELATED TO REPRODUCTIVE TRACT INFECTION AMONG COMMUNITIES OF COLOR
    United States; California; Women--Health and hygiene--United States
  - Tides Center (09851899), 1998 September 01-1999 August 31 (Reel R8176)
    SUPPORT FOR THE INSITE PROJECT TO CONVENE A MEETING ON PARENTS' ROLES AS SEXUALITY EDUCATORS FOR THEIR CHILDREN
    United States; Sex instruction; Parenting--Study and teaching
  - Tides Center (09851908), 1998 September 01-1999 August 31 (Reel R8224)
    United States; Nature--Effect of human beings on; Indians of North America-- Government relations; Radioactive waste disposal--Government policy; Indians of North America -- Land tenure; American bison
  - Tides Center (09900267), 1999 January 01-2000 December 31 (Reel R8683)
    SUPPORT FOR THE CENTER'S URBAN HABITAT PROGRAM'S REGIONAL ORGANIZING FOR SMART GROWTH AND ENVIRONMENTAL JUSTICE
    Miller-Travis, Vernice
    San Francisco (Calif.); Urban renewal--California--San Francisco (Calif.)--Citizen participation
  - Tides Center (09901495), 1999 August 01-2002 July 31 (Reel R8483)
    California; Youth--United States--Citizen participation; Leadership; Community development -- California
  - Tides Center (09951816), 1999 September 01-2002 August 31 (Reel R8555)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR GRANTMAKERS FOR EDUCATION
    $30,000.00;$15,000.00
    United States; Education -- United States; Humanitarianism--United States
  - Tides Center (10100270), 2000 May 01-2001 February 28 (Reel R8708)
    Planning grant for the development of an International Center on Transitional Justice
    Global; Civil society -- Global; Human rights
  - Tides Foundation (08600100), 1986 January 01-1992 April 30 (Reel R6557)
    SUPPORT FOR A FORESTRY DEVELOPMENT PROJECT TO ASSIST LOW-INCOME HISPANIC COMMUNITIES IN NEW MEXICO
    $542,000.00;$542,000.00
  - Tides Foundation (08900201), 1988 November 01-1990 June 30 (Reel R7989)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON FEDERAL & STATE POLICIES FOR SUSTAINABLE AGRICULTURE AND GROUNDWATER PROTECTION
  - Tides Foundation (08950165), 1988 December 01-1989 November 30 (Reel R5841)
    STUDY TO DETERMINE THE POTENTIAL FOR DEVELOPING COMPUTER-BASED NETWORKS FOR NON-GOVERNMENTAL ORGANIZATIONS IN DEVELOPING COUNTRIES
    Heisler, Michele;Wollenberg, Eva
    Central America; South America; SouthEast Asia
  - Tides Foundation (09100478), 1991 January 01-1992 December 31 (Reel R7067)
  - Tides Foundation (09100482), 1991 March 11-1993 August 01 (Reel R6574)
    SUPPORT FOR THE FOREST TRUST'S COLLABORATIVE ACTIVITIES WITH GROUPS FOCUSING ON RURAL DEVELOPMENT IN U.S. FORESTED AREAS
  - Tides Foundation (09200734), 1992 June 01-1997 March 31 (Reel R7195)
    FOR THE FOREST TRUST'S COORDINATION OF THE NATIONAL NETWORK OF FOREST PRACTITIONERS AND ITS RURAL DEVELOPMENT WORK IN THE SOUTHWEST
    $1,025,000.00;$1,025,000.00
    United States; Rural development--United States; Forests and forestry -- United States
  - Tides Foundation (09250826), 1992 March 01-1993 August 31 (Reel R6420)
    TO INCREASE NGO PARTICIPATION IN DEVELOPING A NEW WORLD BANK POLICY FOR WATER RESOURCES MANAGEMENT
  - Tides Foundation (09250962), 1992 June 01-1992 November 30 (Reel R6288)
    PROJECT SUPPORT FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF THE CENTER FOR REPRODUCTIVE LAW AND POLICY (RHG)
  - Tides Foundation (09251213), 1992 July 01-1992 December 31 (Reel R6550)
    SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE TO PLAN NGO ACTIVITIES FOLLOWING THE 1992 U.N. CONFERENCE ON ENVIRONMENT AND DEVELOPMENT
  - Tides Foundation (09251407), 1992 October 01-1993 August 31 (Reel R6624)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE PLANNING ACTIVITIES OF THE ADVOCACY NETWORK FOR DEVELOPMENT
  - Tides Foundation (09351520), 1993 July 01-1995 June 30 (Reel R6850)
    GRANT FUNDS WOULD PROVIDE STAFF SUPPORT FOR THE GRANTMAKERS INCOME SECURITY TASK FORCE
    Elliott, Mark D.;Lipsky, Michael;Mincy, Ronald B.
  - Tides Foundation (09400138), 1993 September 01-1997 April 30 (Reel R7188)
    ANALYSIS OF U.S. DEPARTMENT OF AGRICULTURE BUDGET AND APPROPRIATION POLICIES
    $299,988.00;$299,988.00
    Coward, E. Walter;Olson, Jeffrey T.
    United States; Agricultural subsidies -- United States
  - Tides Foundation (09450307), 1993 September 01-1994 August 31 (Reel R6816)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR FUNDERS CONCERNED ABOUT AIDS, AN AFFINITY GROUP COORDINATING A PHILANTHROPIC RESPONSE TO AIDS
  - Tides Foundation (09450321), 1993 October 01-1994 December 31 (Reel R7184)
    SUPPORT FOR THE SOUTHERN RURAL DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE
    Southern States; Rural development--Southern States
  - Tides Foundation (09450482), 1994 January 01-1994 December 31 (Reel R6806)
    SUPPORT FOR THE HEALTH AND DEVELOPMENT POLICY PROJECT TO FOSTER DIALOGUE ON US POPULATION POLICIES AND PROGRAMS
  - Tides Foundation (09450606), 1994 March 01-1995 March 31 (Reel R7331)
    SUPPORTS RADIO SERIES "PEOPLE AND THE PLANET: RETHINKING POPULATION" LEADING UP TO INTERNATIONAL CONFERENCE ON POPULATION & DEVELOP.
  - Tides Foundation (09500320), 1994 December 01-1997 November 30 (Reel R6918)
    SUPPORT FOR THE NATIONAL FUNDING COLLABORATIVE ON VIOLENCE PREVENTION TO SUPPORT LOCAL COLLABORATIVES
    Urban Poverty Program [UP];Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ];Governance And Public Policy Program [GPP];Education & Culture Program [EC]
    $800,000.00;$300,000.00
    Franklin, Robert;Mohamed, Inca A.;Molnar, Janice M.;Petrovich, Janice;Seltzer, Michael
  - Tides Foundation (09500780), 1994 October 01-1995 September 30 (Reel R6812)
  - Tides Foundation (09500946), 1995 July 01-1997 June 30 (Reel R7639)
    SUPPORT FOR EXPANSION OF THE STUDENTS FOR RESPONSIBLE BUSINESS COMMUNITY DEVELOPMENT INITIATIVE
  - Tides Foundation (09501141), 1995 June 01-1996 November 30 (Reel R7295)
    TO ADVANCE MEDIA, COMMUNICATIONS AND INFORMATION PROGRAMS IN PREPARATION FOR, AND AT, THE UN FOURTH WORLD CONFERENCE ON WOMEN
    Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ];Governance And Public Policy Program [GPP];International Affairs Program [IA];Reproductive Health And Population Program [RHP];US & International Affairs Programs - Office Of Vice President [USIAP/OVP];Urban Poverty
    Elliott, Mark D.;Hempel, Margaret L.;Mensah, Lisa A.;Neuborne, Helen;Santos, John Phillip;Smith, Marcia A.;Zwerling, L. Steven
  - Tides Foundation (09501224), 1995 July 01-1997 June 30 (Reel R7330)
    SUPPORT FOR THE HEALTH AND DEVELOPMENT POLICY PROJECT FOR POLICY AND PROGRAM ANALYSIS, MONITORING AND EDUCATION
  - Tides Foundation (09550661), 1995 April 01-1996 May 31 (Reel R7649, Reel R8157)
    SUPPORT FOR A COMMUNICATIONS TRAINING PROGRAM FOR YOUTH-LED NON-PROFIT ORGANIZATIONS
    Beckham, Edgar F.;Mohamed, Inca A.
  - Tides Foundation (09550705), 1995 April 01-1996 March 31 (Reel R8199)
    SUPPORT FOR A POLICY WORKSHOP AT THE 1995 FOURTH WORLD CONFERENCE ON WOMEN ON GLOBAL AGRICULTURE AND FOOD CHANGES
  - Tides Foundation (09600318), 1996 January 01-1997 December 31 (Reel R7766)
  - Tides Foundation (09600349), 1995 July 01-1996 June 30 (Reel R6823)
    SUPPORT FOR THE VIOLENCE, SEXUALITY AND HEALTH RIGHTS PROGRAM
    $62,381.00;$62,381.00
  - Tides Foundation (09600435), 1996 April 01-1998 March 31 (Reel R7978)
    SUPPORT TO DEVELOP A CLEARINGHOUSE FOR THE NGO STEERING COMMITTEE FOR THE UN COMMISSION ON SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT
    Conroy, Michael E.;Wasow, Bernard
  - Tides Foundation (09600954), 1996 May 01-1997 April 30 (Reel R7338)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE GRANTMAKERS INCOME SECURITY TASK FORCE
  - Tides Foundation (09650203), 1995 December 01-1997 March 31 (Reel R7312)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE FIRST INDIGENOUS CONFERENCE ON THE ENVIRONMENT IN CENTRAL AMERICA
    International Affairs Program [IA];Latin America & The Caribbean [LAC]
    Cox, Larry;Eguizabal, Cristina
  - Tides Foundation (09701828), 1997 July 01-1998 June 30 (Reel R8046)
    CONTINUED SUPPORT FOR THE GRANTMAKERS INCOME SECURITY TASK FORCE (960-0954)
    Governance and Civil Society;Human Development and Reproductive Health
    Lipsky, Michael;Mincy, Ronald B.
  - Tides Foundation (09801681), 1998 July 01-2000 May 31 (Reel R8164)
    SUPPORT FOR ADVOCACY WOMEN'S RIGHTS IN AREAS OF ARMED CONFLICT
    Global; Peace--Citizen participation--Global; Women's rights--Global
  - Tilton School (06900514), 1969 June 17-1970 August 05 (Reel R1160)
    SUPPORT FOR THE DISSEMINATION OF A WATER POLLUTION RESEARCH PROGRAM FOR SECONDARY SCHOOL STUDENTS
  - Time Dollar (09750407), 1996 December 01-1999 November 30 (Reel R8220)
    SUPPORT FOR A BOOK ON PROMOTING CIVIC RESPONSIBILITY THROUGH LOCAL, TAX-EXEMPT CURRENCY
  - Time Dollar (10201637), 2002 August 01-2003 April 30 (Reel R8983)
    To plan and implement demonstration sites in Brooklyn, Houston and El Paso for the utilization of Time Dollars to cultivate social capital for community asset building
    El Paso (Tex.); Houston (Tex.); Brooklyn (New York, N.Y.)
  - Time Dollar (10450197), 2003 November 01-2004 October 31 (Reel R9233)
    To establish a demonstration site in the Bushwick section of Brooklyn where Time Dollars are blended with public dollars to provide day-care services to low-income immigrant families
    $11,254.00;$11,254.00
  - Tioga County (09701607), 1997 July 01-1998 June 30 (Reel R7730)
    SUPPORT FOR DECATEGORIZED HUMAN SERVICE DELIVERY PROGRAM
  - Tmm Corp., Inc. (10052109), 2000 October 01-2001 September 30 (Reel R8627)
    SUPPORT FOR THE DEVELOPMENT OF A DOCUMENTARY FILM ON TRADITIONAL MEDICINE, ENTITLED THE AFRICAN WAY OF HEALING
    Global; Mass media; Traditional medicine--Africa; Documentary films -- Africa
  - Tmm Corp., Inc. (10200309), 2001 December 01-2002 September 30 (Reel R8791)
    For multimedia production and technical assistance activities to advance public knowledge of African traditional healing practices
    United States; Africa, West; Traditional medicine--Africa; Medicinal plants--Africa; Alternative medicine -- Africa; Mass media
  - Tocantins-Araguaia Foundation (09200312), 1992 January 01-1993 April 30 (Reel R6352, Reel R6705)
    RESEARCH AND TRAINING ON SUSTAINABLE ALTERNATIVES FOR SMALL-SCALE AGRICULTURAL PRODUCTION IN THE EASTERN AMAZON
  - Tocqueville Center, Inc. (06800803), 1968 August 16-1969 August 15 (Reel R1904)
    SUPPORT FOR SEVERAL STUDIES OF THE TOCQUEVILLE SERIES ON U.S. - EUROPEAN RELATIONS
    Kohl, Wilfrid L.
    United States; Europe, Western
  - Tohono Oodham Community Action (09901504), 1999 August 01-2002 July 31 (Reel R8952)
    Arizona; Youth--United States--Citizen participation; Leadership; Community development -- Arizona
  - Toledo Orchestra Association (06600325), 1966 July 01-1976 June 30 (Reel R2935, Reel R2936, Reel R4342)
  - Tomas Film (09950991), 1999 May 01-2000 April 30 (Reel R8752)
    SUPPORT FOR A DOCUMENTARY FILM ON NEW MUSIC FROM AFRICA AND ITS RELATIONSHIP TO MODES OF AFRICAN TRANSPORTATION
    $62,975.00;$62,975.00
    Africa, Southern; Documentary films -- Africa; Music--Africa, Southern; Transportation--Africa--Social aspects
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (08900118), 1988 November 01-1990 August 31 (Reel R5948)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR COMPLETION OF A COMMUNITY NEEDS ASSESSMENT PROJECT
    $174,616.00;$174,616.00
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (08900120), 1988 November 01-1990 August 31 (Reel R5948)
    SUPPORT FOR A CONFERENCE OF LOCAL, FOUNDATION-SUPORTED HISPANIC POLICY CENTERS AND NEEDS ASSESSMENT PROJECTS.
    $31,336.00;$31,336.00
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (08900344), 1988 October 01-1990 July 31 (Reel R6218)
    SUPPORT TO DEVELOP A PROFILE OF THE HISPANIC TEACHER POOL AND IDENTIFY HISPANIC TEACHER PRODUCERS
    Hatton, Barbara R.
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (08901314), 1989 July 01-1990 March 31 (Reel R6226)
    TO SUPPORT RESEARCH IN VALUE-ADDED INTERVENTIONS AMONG HISPANIC TEACHER PRODUCERS, IDENTIFICATION OF POSSIBLE CONSORTIUM MEMBERS, AND PROPOSAL DEVELOPMENT
    $166,330.00;$166,330.00
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (09101324), 1991 September 01-1995 May 31 (Reel R6655)
    COMPLETION OF ACTION PLAN BASED ON RESULTS OF THE HOUSTON EVALUATION OF COMMUNITY PRIORITIES PROJECT
    Houston (Tex.)
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (09150937), 1991 July 01-1992 June 30 (Reel R6105)
    TO CONDUCT AN ORGANIZATIONAL ASSESSMENT AND PLANNING PROCESS
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (09300614), 1993 May 01-1995 April 30 (Reel R6779)
    SUPPORT FOR POLICY ANALYSIS REGARDING LATINOS IN CALIFORNIA
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (09551441), 1995 September 01-1997 February 28 (Reel R7091)
    RESEARCH ON AFFIRMATIVE ACTION PROGRAMS IN EDUCATION, EMPLOYMENT AND BUSINESS
    United States; Affirmative action programs -- United States; Hispanic Americans -- Political activity
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (09600967), 1996 June 01-2000 March 31 (Reel R8695)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR A PROJECT ON "THE LATINO COMMUNITY AND U.S. FOREIGN RELATIONS"
    International Affairs Program [IA];Rights And Social Justice Program [RSJ]
    $445,000.00;$445,000.00
    Ispahani, Mahnaz Z.;Romero, Anthony D.
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (09651028), 1996 July 01-1997 June 30 (Reel R7920)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH OF ALTERNATIVE TEACHER CERTIFICATION PROGRAMS AS A MEANS OF AUGMENTING THE POOL OF MINORITY TEACHERS
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (09700428), 1997 January 01-1998 December 31 (Reel R8077)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON CIVIL RIGHTS ISSUES AND ORGANIZATIONAL DEVELOPMENT ACTIVITIES
    Jenkins, Alan;Smith, Marcia A.
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (09701164), 1997 June 01-1998 December 31 (Reel R8117)
    MONITORING AND RESEARCH ON THE IMPLEMENTATION AND IMPACT OF RECENT IMMIGRATION AND WELFARE LEGISLATION
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (09702014), 1997 September 01-2000 January 31 (Reel R8258)
    SUPPORT FOR STUDY OF THE IMPACT AND DEVELOPMENT POTENTIAL OF REMITTANCES SENT TO LATIN AMERICA
    Mexico and Central America (Mexico City);PSJ - Office of the Vice President;Human Rights
    $295,000.00;$295,000.00
    Farias Campero, Pablo;Higashi, Taryn;Ispahani, Mahnaz Z.;McClymont, Mary (Mary E.)
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (09851906), 1998 August 01-1999 February 28 (Reel R8189)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH ON INSTITUTIONAL OBSTACLES TO COLLEGEPREPARATION IN CALIFORNIA PUBLIC HIGH SCHOOLS
    California; Educational equalization -- California; Minorities--Education--California
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (09900569), 1999 February 01-2001 December 31 (Reel R9016)
    SUPPORT FOR STUDIES FOR LATINO POLITICAL PARTICIPATION AND SOCIAL AND ECONOMIC INCLUSION
    Eguizabal, Cristina;Rios, Sara;Santos, John Phillip;Smith, Marcia A.
    United States; Latin America; Political participation--United States; Hispanic Americans -- Political activity
  - Toms Rivera Policy Institute (10250188), 2001 November 01-2003 April 30 (Reel R9037)
    For applied research on the institutional, legal and social barriers limiting Latino advancement in diverse school systems and labor markets
    Rios, Sara
    United States; Hispanic Americans -- Research; Educational equalization -- Research; Affirmative action programs -- Research
  - Tomsk Human Rights Research Centre (09750295), 1997 January 01-1997 December 31 (Reel R8759)
    SUPPORT FOR A PROJECT TO MONITOR HUMAN RIGHTS OBSERVANCE IN WESTERN SIBERIA
  - Tomsk Human Rights Research Centre (09850326), 1998 January 01-1999 December 31 (Reel R8303, Reel R8387)
    CONTINUED SUPPORT FOR HUMAN RIGHTS MONITORING AND DEFENSE IN WESTERN SIBERIA
    Russia; Human rights advocacy -- Russia (Federation) -- Siberia, Western
  - Tomsk Regional International Historical, Educational, Human Rights and Charitable Society "Memorial" (10050574), 2000 March 01-2001 December 31 (Reel R9180)
    SUPPORT FOR A DATABASE OF THE REPRESSED IN TOMSK REGION DURING THE SOVIET PERIOD, AND FOR THE MEMORIAL MUSEUM AND ITS PUBLIC EDUCATION WORK
    Russia; Political persecution--Russia (Federation)--Archives; Databases -- Russia (Federation); Refugee Camps--Russia (Federation)
  - Tonantzin Land Institute (08850610), 1988 April 01-1990 March 31 (Reel R6116)
    SUPPORT FOR A TECHNICAL ASSISTANCE PROJECT IN NORTHERN NEW MEXICO
  - Tonantzin Land Institute (09200612), 1992 February 01-1994 May 31 (Reel R6675)
    SUPPORT TO IMPLEMENT AN INNOVATIVE WATER ADJUDICATION PROGRAM IN THE RIO MIMBRES REGION OF SOUTHWESTERN NEW MEXICO
    $92,500.00;$92,500.00
  - Tonantzin Land Institute (09450949), 1994 July 01-1995 June 30 (Reel R7123)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR AN INTERN AT THE OFFICE OF ENVIRONMENTAL POLICY TO ASSIST IN PREPARATIONS FOR THE "SUMMIT OF THE AMERICAS"
    Western Hemisphere
  - Tonantzin Land Institute (09751736), 1997 August 01-1999 March 31 (Reel R7897)
    PARTIAL SUPPORT FOR THE ACEQUIA PUBLIC EDUCATION PROJECT
  - Tony Batten Productions, Inc. (08650330), 1986 March 20-1986 December 19 (Reel R4534)
    RESEARCH AND PLANNING A TELEVISION DOCUMENTARY SERIES ON THE BLACK POPULATION IN THE UNITED STATES
    $19,463.00;$19,463.00
  - Topiwala National Medical College (06200475), 1962 September 24-1967 March 31 (Reel R2634, Reel R3923)
    INSTITUTIONAL SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH IN REPRODUCTIVE BIOLOGY IN INDIA
    $125,000.00;$54,456.36
  - Topsham Conservation Commission (07450110), 1973 November 30-1976 June 30 (Reel R1399)
    PREPARATION OF AN INVENTORY OF THE TOWN'S OPENLAND AREAS FOR FURTHER WORK IN OPEN SPACE PROTECTION AND LAND USE PLANNING
    $750.00;$750.00
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (06200026), 1961 November 21-1964 November 20 (Reel R0709, Reel R3903)
    GENERAL SUPPORT FOR THE CENTER FOR ECONOMIC RESEARCH IN BUENOS AIRES
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (06300381), 1963 June 11-1966 June 10 (Reel R0711, Reel R3189, Reel R3916, Reel R4524)
    PROGRAM OF ECONOMIC RESEARCH AND TRAINING ON PROBLEMS OF DEVELOPMENT PLANNING IN ARGENTINA
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (06300570), 1963 October 08-1964 October 07 (Reel R0712, Reel R3424, Reel R3425)
    CONFERENCE ON PROBLEMS OF ECONOMIC AND SOCIAL DEVELOPMENT IN LATIN AMERICA
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (06400294), 1964 June 03-1968 June 02 (Reel R2058, Reel R3427)
    CENTER FOR RESEARCH IN PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION AT THE INSTITUTE IN ARGENTINA
    $263,000.00;$263,000.00
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (06600176), 1966 April 08-1969 April 07 (Reel R1796, Reel R1846, Reel R3428)
    DEVELOPMENTAL SUPPORT OF THE INSTITUTES CENTER FOR ECONOMIC RESEARCH
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (06700101), 1967 January 18-1972 September 30 (Reel R4807)
    RESEARCH ON ECONOMIC DEVELOPMENT AND INTEGRATION IN LATIN AMERICA
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (06700282), 1967 May 24-1968 May 23 (Reel R1878, Reel R3431)
    SUPPORT FOR CENTER FOR URBAN AND REGIONAL STUDIES
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (06700286), 1967 May 25-1971 October 01 (Reel R1834, Reel R3432)
    SUPPORT FOR CENTER FOR EDUCATIONAL RESEARCH
    Office Of Vice President -Finance & Administration;Andean Region and Southern Cone (Santiago)
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (06800143), 1967 July 01-1970 January 28 (Reel R2692)
    RESEARCH ON MARGINAL POPULATIONS IN LATIN AMERICA
    $194,000.00;$193,586.04
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (06800572), 1968 June 14-1979 December 31 (Reel R2681, Reel R2682, Reel R2683, Reel R2684, Reel R3180, Reel R3181, Reel R3432, Reel R3433)
    SUPPORT FOR THE INSTITUTE'S SOCIAL SCIENCES CENTERS
    $3,040,000.00;$3,040,000.00
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (06800892), 1968 October 03-1975 November 16 (Reel R2972, Reel R2973, Reel R2974, Reel R3848)
    RESEARCH SUPPORT FOR THE LATIN AMERICAN COUNCIL OF SOCIAL SCIENCES
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (07200265), 1972 July 05-1974 January 04 (Reel R1747, Reel R3888)
    SUPPORT FOR A RESEARCH PROJECT AT THE CENTER FOR RESEARCH IN PUBLIC ADMINISTRATION
    $22,300.00;$.00
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (07200454), 1972 October 13-1976 October 12 (Reel R2825, Reel R3265, Reel R3473)
    SUPPORT FOR LATIN AMERICAN GRADUATIE TRAINING PROGRAM IN URBAN & REGIONAL PLANNING
    $150,400.00;$149,870.98
    Argentina; Latin America
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (07350644), 1973 April 02-1974 April 01 (Reel R1382, Reel R4277, Reel R4612)
    SUPPORT FOR RESEARCH
    $4,060.00;$4,060.00
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (07450677), 1974 July 01-1974 December 31 (Reel R1197, Reel R4276)
    TO ASSIST IN THE PREPARATION OF A GUIDE FOR HISTORICAL RESEARCH IN ARGENTINA
    Dye, Richard W.
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (07550049), 1974 October 22-1975 January 21 (Reel R1189)
    THIRD SEMINAR OF LATIN AMERICAN EDUCATIONAL RESEARCH CENTERS
    $5,000.00;$3,379.24
  - Torcuato Di Tella Institute (09050111), 1989 October 01-1990 October 01 (Reel R5908)
    SUPPORT FOR A SYMPOSIUM ON THE WORK OF ALBERT O. HIRSCHMAN AND ITS IMPLICATIONS FOR DEVELOPMENT STRATEGIES IN LATIN AMERICA
    $15,105.00;$14,590.00